Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Files 6104
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1969-2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold
6104
18 cubic feet
18 linear ft.
Records.
5798890
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 27, 2004
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5281: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5512: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5551: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5620: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5659: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5727: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5786: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5825: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5861: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5913: Arnold Zack Additional Aarbitration Files 5950: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Cases 5979: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6049: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Cases 6066: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6141: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 6250: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial; Collective bargaining -- Police; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial; Collective bargaining -- Service industries; Collective bargaining -- Stevedores; Collective bargaining -- Steel industry; Collective bargaining -- School administrators; Collective bargaining -- Public utilities; Collective bargaining -- Transportation; Collective bargaining -- Teachers; Zack, Arnold
5798890
- Adams County 14/Teachers Association, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  4/28/1997
- Andrew Levy Association/South Africa, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  10/23/1997
- Amtrack PEB, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Sep-97
- Arlington/Patrolmen's Betterment Association, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  3/27/1997
- Barnstable Mediation (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bay State Gas/UWUA 273, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  12/16/1997
- Bermuda Docks (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bermuda, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  3/4/1994
- Bermuda Fire Services, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Mar-97
- Bemis Association/USWA 506, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  12/22/1997
- Bermuda, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  March/April 1997
- Bradley Memorial/CHCA, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  4/24/1997
- BSC/BTU 66, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  5/14/1997
- Brown University (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Central Maine/Local 128, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  9/10/1997
- Chapin & Bangs/United Steelworkers 8831, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  5/5/1997
- Chittenden County/IBT Local 597, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  10/9/1997
- Comm. of Massachusetts Office of Employee Relations/AFSCME 93, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  4/8/1997
- CUNO/UPWIU, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  6/24/1997
- Conway Ed./Conway School Board/NEA, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  11/13/1997
- Derry/IAFF 2620, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  12/29/1997
- Durham/FF, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  11/3/1997
- Electric Boat Corp/IBEW 261, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  1/7/1997
- Epic Longo/Teamsters local 42, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  11/24/1997
- Epping/Education Association, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  1/15/1997
- Hartford Board of Education/Federation of Teachers, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  6/17/1997
- Hartford Board of Education/Federation of Teachers, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  10/11/1997
- Hollingsworth & Vose/UPIU 880, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  10/21/1997
- Hollingsworth & Vose, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  1/10/1997
- Hollingsworth & Vose/UPIU 880, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  12/3/1997
- Homestead Baking, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  10/14/1997
- IRS/NTEU, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  5/12/1997
- IRS/NTEU, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  11/19-20/97
- J&J Corrugated Box (Box 2, Folder 9)
  no date
- Kinney Vacuum/ UAW 1596, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  10/24/1997
- Laconia School Board/Education Assisants, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  1/9/1997
- Lynn/IAFF, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  2/13/1997
- Lynn/Police, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  5/7/1997
- Littleton School Board/ Support Staff, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  1/17/1997
- Metropolitan Opera/AGMA, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  4/29/1997
- Macy's/ Local 1-s RWDSU, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  11/27/1996
- Milton Hershey School/BCTW local 464, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  9/11/1997
- NMB PEB 232 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- New England Telephone/IBEW 2322, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  2/11/1997
- New York Police, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Aug-97
- New York/Police, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  6/3/1997
- Poland Springs/UFCW 1445, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  11/5/1996
- Quebec Corp., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  11/25/1997
- Rogo/Teamsters 1035, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  5/29/1997
- Scott Press, INC./ MLA Local 1, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  3/25/1997
- Shaws Supermarkets/UFCW 791, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  9/30/1997
- Springfield/Teachers Association, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  1/17/1996
- Shaws Supermarkets/UFCW, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  11/18/1997
- Shaws Supermarkets/UFCW 791, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  4/14/1997
- Shaws Supermarkets/UFCW 791, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  1/14/1997
- Southern Connecticut Gas Company/USWA, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  9/8/1997
- Sullivan County Nursing Home/AFSCME, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  4/11/1997
- UCLA Ben Aaron Lecture Series, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  5/1/1997
- UConn Health Center/UHP local 3837, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  4/30/1997
- UConn Health Center/UHP 3837, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  9/29/1997
- UPS Clarification, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  7/18/1997
- Union Trustees/Newspaper Guild, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  2/12/1997
- West Warwick/Rhode Island Council 94 AFSCME, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  12/27/1996
- ABC/NABET local 16, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Jul-98
- Extra Copy of Briefs-ABC (Box 3, Folder 19)
- ABC-Company Exhibit 25, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  (Timesheets-1997 Monday Night Football)
- ABC Exhibit 24, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  (1996 Timesheets)
- ABC/NABET, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ABC/NABET, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  6/9/1998
- ABC/NABET Master Agreements, 1985-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- ABC/NABET Schedule Change Grievances, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- ABC/NABET Schedule Changes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- ABC/NABET, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  10/6/1998
- ABC/NABET, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  11/10/1998
- ABC/NABET, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  12/30/1998
- Arlington/PBA, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  4/13/1998
- Bardon Trimount/Teamsters local 42, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  2/25/1998
- Baystate Bus/ATU 1547, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  9/11/1998
- Bermuda: G. Fubler Sinking of Xiang Da, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  2/20-3/3/98
- Bermuda Industrial/ Department of Marine & Ports, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  4/15/1998
- Xiang Da Sinking, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  4/15/1997
- Bermuda: Stevedoring/Hamilton Valcleners, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Jan/Feb 1998
- Bermuda Industrial Union- Hamilton ValCleners & Paget DryCleaners, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  1/27/1998
- Blackstone/AFSCME 93, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  9/18/1997
- Boston Gas, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  1/12/1998
- Brown University/SEIU Local 134, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  6/29/1998
- Brown University/SEIU 134, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  1/6/1998
- Cambridge/Cambridge Police, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  9/14/1998
- Cleveland/Police Association, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  9/4/1997
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts /SEIU 509, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  9/22-23/98
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts/SEIU 509, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Consolidated Rail Corp/ Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Conrail/BMWE, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  1/13/1998
- Corp. Bros, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  6/22/1998
- Danvers Police, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  3/13/1998
- Albert Einstein College/Local 1199, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  10/23/1998
- Federation of Technical College Teachers/Community Technical Colleges, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- St. Joseph Health Services of Rhode Island/FNHP 5018, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  10/14/1998
- FOUR/UNITE, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  7/9/1998
- UNITE, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  12/17/1997
- Good Samaritan/MNA, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  2/17/1997
- Hopkinton School, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  4/27/1998
- IRS/NTEU, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  9/17/98 Schillaci Stay
- IRS/NTEU, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  917/98
- Union's Post Hearing Brief-Removal of Robert Schillaci (Box 6, Folder 3)
- IRS/NTEU Stay, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  3/10-11/97
- IRS/NTEU, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  6/26/1998
- IRS, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  4/10/1998
- IRS, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  4/11/1998
- IRS, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  5/27/1998
- Interlakes School District/Interlakes Education Association, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  6/11/1998
- IRS/NTEU, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  9/1/1998
- IRS/NTEU, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  2/23/1998
- Kinney Vacuum/UAW 1596, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  5/7/1998
- Lucent Technologies/IBEW 1522, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  7/15/1998
- Lucent Technologies/IBEW 152, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  3/5/1999
- Lynn, City of/AFSCME 93, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  12/16/1998
- Madison Square Garden/IBEW, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  7/16/1998
- MA Department of Dispute Resolution/Citibank, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  4/29/1998
- Manchester School Committee/Education Association, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  3/8,11,12/96
- Metro Opera/AGMA, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  5/4/1998
- Mount Sinai/Brotherhood of Security, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  9/19/1996
- Madison Square Garden/IBEW 1212, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  1/11/1999
- New England Power/BUWNE local 345, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  2/18/1998
- New Fairfield board of Education/UNISERV, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  1/19/1998
- New Haven Board of Education/Teachers Association, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  5/28/1998
- Norfolk Superior Court Mediation, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  11/20/1998
- New Haven Board of Education/Federation of Teachers, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  3/16/1998
- NYNEX/IBEW 2321, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  6/30/1998
- Overseas Federation of Teachers, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  2/2-6/98
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  5/20/1998
- Pennsylvania Power & Light, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  1/26/1999
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  6/25/1997
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  1/8/1998
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  1/9&14/98
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  1/9 & 2/10 1998
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- City of New York/PBA, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  4/27/1997
- Philadelphia School District/Federation of Teachers, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  1/8/1997
- Philadelphia School District/Federation of Teachers, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  4/10/1997
- Philadelphia School District, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia School District/Federation of Teachers, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  2/10/1997
- Pepperell/AFSCME 93, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  6/10/1997
- Pennsylvnia Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  12/18/1997
- Philadelphia School District/Federation of Teachers, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  5/19/1997
- Philadelphia School District/Federation of Teachers, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Pueblo School District #60/Pueblo Education Association, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Feb-97
- Pennsylvania Power & Light, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  1/30/1998
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  1/28/1998
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW 1600, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  1/7/1998
- Pennsylvania Power & Light, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Pennsylvania Power & Light, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Pennsylvania Power & Light U-39, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania Power & Light U-38, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Pennsylvania Power & Light U-37, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Pennsylvania Power & Light, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania Power & Light U-36, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Power & Light U-35, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Newspapers/Local 628, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  1/29/1998
- Plymouth County Sheriff Department/MCOFU, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  11/9/1998
- Providence Gas & Steel, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  5/19/1998
- Providence Journal, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  7/13/1998
- Shaws Supermarkets/UFCW 791, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  3/12/1998
- Shaws Supermarkets, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  10/15/1998
- Shaws Supermarkets, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  6/8/1998
- Trinity Hill/NEHCEU, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  8/26/1996
- TWA/IAM Discharge, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  5/11-12/98
- IAM Grievance #25967 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- UPS/IBT local 25, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  7/17/1998
- Wallingford, Town of/Wallingford Police Union, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  5/5/1998
- Wallingford vs. AFSCME 15, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  3/9/1998
- Warwick/Warwick FOP #7, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  5/18/1998
- Weston School/Teachers, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  5/7 & 5/15 1998
- EBT Dispute Arbitration Documents (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
- DoDDS/OFT (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  1/7/1999
- DoDDS/OFT (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
  7/3/1999
- DoDDS/OFT (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
  5/6/1999
- USWA Financial Officer's Manual (Box 11, Folder 7)
- USWA/Steelworkers Staff Representatives Union (Box 11, Folder 8)
  5/3/1999
- USWA International Union/Staff Representatives Union (Box 11, Folder 9)
  12/31/1998
- USWA, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- USWA - Planning a Strike Assistance Program for Your Local Union, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- USWA, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- USWA, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- USWA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- USWA, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Wellesley, Town of/Local 1795 IAFF, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Wellesley, Town of/Local 1795 IAFF, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  11/21/1997
- Wellesley, Town of/Local 1795 IAFF, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- New Hampshire State Employees, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  April/may 1999
- OFT/DoDD (clarification), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  8/3/1999
- Pennsylvania Power & Light, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  6/10/1999
- Pennsylvania Power & Light/IBEW, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  9/10/1998
- Plymouth County Sheriff's Department/MCOFU (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Providence Journal/Local 12, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  4/16/1997
- PWA Decor/IBT 437, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  2/3/1999
- RTA Transit/Amalgamated Transit Union, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  9/4/1998
- Salem, Town of/ Town Employees, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  2/2/1999
- Shaughnessy-Kaplan Rehab Hospital, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  9/2/1998
- Shaws Supermarkets/UFCW local 791, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  11/4/1998
- Shaws Supermarkets/UFCW 791, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Duxbury School Committee/Local 1700 AFSCME, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  1/30/1996
- Duxbury School Committee/Local 1700 AFSCME, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  5/8/1996
- Duxbury School Committee/Local 1700 AFSCME, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  5/10/1996
- Duxbury School Committee/Local 1700 AFSCME, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- IRS and NTEU Chapter 271, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  4/27/1999
- IRS/NTEU, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- New York Board of Education/Local 891 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- United University Professors, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  9/21/1999
- City of Philadelphia, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  10/27/1999
- Shaws Supermarket, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  1/27/1999
- Shaws Supermarket, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  1/14/2000
- SMG of Rhode Island, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  3/1/1999
- Collective Bargaining Agreements Town of Wellesley, 1993-1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Manual for Conciliators (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Draft Manual for Conciliators, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- ILO Settlement Cases (Box 13, Folder 4)
- ILO Voluntary Arbitration (Box 13, Folder 5)
- ILO Grievance Arbitration Monograph (Box 13, Folder 6)
- ABC/NABET, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  9/16/1998
- ABC/NABET, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  3/10/1999
- ABC/NABET, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  9/14/1999
- ABC/NABET, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  10/20/1999
- ABC/NABET, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  10/26/1999
- Acton Mediation, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  12/13/1999
- Bellingham, Town, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  9/28/1999
- Berlin Police Comm./New Hampshire, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  6/8/1999
- Bloomfield Board of Education/Bloomfield Education Association, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  1/8/1999
- Boston Edison/UWUA 369, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  11/25/1998
- Boston Gas/United Steelworkers, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  6/12/1998
- Braintree/UWUA Local 466, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  5/29/1998
- Bristol/IBPO 304, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  6/10/1998
- Cardoza Law School Lecture, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  4/12/1999
- Casey & Hayes, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  10/19/1998
- Con-Val School District, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  1/13/1999
- Cooley, Inc./Awn. Finishers, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  11/2/1998
- Cornell NYC, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Crowley/Acme Print Co, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  6/11/1999
- Derry, Town of/local 1801, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  9/9/1999
- Dyecraftsman/UNITE, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  9/13/1999
- Education Alliance/DC 1707, Local 215, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  2/26/1999
- "Excelleration", 1999 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  4/20/1999
- Federal Labor Relations Conference, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  6/14-15/99
- Good Samaritan Medical Center/Local 767, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Great Scott Food Markets/UFCW 328, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  2/15/1999
- Greenwood Cemetary/IBEW 966, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  1/14/1999
- DoDDS/OFT, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  10/26-31/98
- Department of Treasury/US Customs Service, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
  1/20/2000
- NTEU/Customs Service (National Agreement & Promotion Plan), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- NTEU/US Customs Service National Agreement, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  10/3/1996
- NTEU/US Customs Service, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  3/17/2000
- NTEU/US Customs Service, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  4/3/2000
- NTEU, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Groton, Town of/USWA 9411, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  10/18/1999
- Hampden County Sheriff/IBCO 248, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  2/10/1999
- Hampden, Town of/IBPO 583, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  4/9/1999
- Hartford Board of Education, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  3/26/1999
- Heating Oil Partners, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  10/22/1999
- IFPTE Local 400/State of Rhode Island, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  10/13/1998
- IRS/NTEU, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  10/7/1998
- IRS/NTEU, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  5/19/1999
- IRS/NTEU, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  3/2/1999
- IRS/NTEU, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  11/30/1998
- Kirschner, Joseph Co. & 1445 UFCW, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  5/13/1999
- Andrew Levy, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  3/3/1999
- Manchester Transit Authority, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  5/17/1999
- New England Power Service/Local 345 BUWN, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  9/3/1998
- Newton/Municipal Employees, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  1/6/1999
- SMG of Rhode Island, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  1/5/1999
- Snap on Tools/UAW 1596, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  10/29/1999
- Joseph Stomel & Sons/Local 51 IBT, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  4/7/1999
- United Steelworkers/Staff Representatives Union, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority /Local 1931 AFSCME, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  2/16/1999
- Timewarner/Newspaper Guild, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  1/26/2000
- Union Industries/USWA Local 4652, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  9/8/1999
- Union Leader Corp/ 271 GCIU (Box 15, Folder 8)
- UPS/Teamsters, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  10/25/1999
- UNITE/FOUR, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  3/29/1999
- UPS/IBT 177, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  10/4/1999
- Warren, Town of/US Steelworkers (Box 15, Folder 12)
- WGBH/NABET, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  3/3/2000
- US Customs/NTEU, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  5/25-26/99
- Wellesley, Town of/IAFF, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  4/21/1999
- Cambridge, City of/Cambridge Police Superior Officers Association, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Cambridge, City of/Cambridge Police Superior Officers Assn, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- New York Board of Education/Local 891 IUOE, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 18-21)
  11/18/1996
- Arbitrations, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder All)
- Arbitrations, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder All)
- Arbitrations, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder All)